前情提要
Previously on Lost Girl...
我们应该保护她的
We should have protected her.
她都不想见我们
She doesn't even want to see us.
你是人类
You're human.
你终于来了
You're finally here.
我一直都在这里
I've always been here.
Rainer会让你团灭Una Mens 别这么做
Rainer will ask you to slay the Una Mens, don't do it.
他们的力量会被重组进一粒种子里
Their power will be amassed into a single remaining seed.
有人从我这里把种子偷走了
It was stolen from me.
你见到的那个恶人 会不会是我的父亲?
That evil that you met, could he be my father?
那个人 会不计一切代价找到他的理想伴侣
That thing, would have done anything to claim his ideal mate
即使那个伴侣是他自己所创造的
even if it meant creating her himself.
好我们有 僵尸唱蓝调
Alright, we got, Zombies that sing the blues
或者性感僵尸医生回大学
or Sexy Vampire Doctor goes back to college
因为他迷失了自己?
because he lost his way?
就这么多了吗?
Is that it?
*Jerry MaGuire：汤姆·克鲁斯96年励志轻喜剧*
我还有〈甜心先生〉
I also have Jerry MaGuire.
不 我是说Bo和流浪者 他们就这样了吗?
No, I mean with Bo and The Wanderer. Is that just it?
我不知道 她把我拒之门外了 行吗?
I dunno, she locked me out, okay?
我和她做了四年好闺密
Four years I've been her best friend.
我知道她所有事情
I know everything about her.
每一次心碎 每一次流泪 结果就这样 我被打入冷宫了
Every heart break, every tear.And just like that, I'm out.
所以如果你不介意 我想忘掉这一切
Okay so if you wouldn't mind, I'd like to forget about it all
然后就看点僵尸片 好吗?
and just watch some Zombie movies, okay?
我喜欢僵尸
I like Zombies.
激烈的爱爱 团灭Una Mens以后 稍作休息吗?
Taking a break from athletic shower sex, post-slaughtering the Una Mens?
我早就想和你谈谈了
I have been meaning to talk to you.
噢 那Dyson和Lauren呢?
Oh yeah, how about Dyson and Lauren?
总有一天吧 你想要我说什么?
One day...What do you want me to say?
我想要你说 你没有被洗脑
I want you to say: you're not brainwashed.
告诉我 我还拥有我最好的朋友
I want you to say I still have a best friend.
当然你还有我这个最好的朋友 还有我没有被洗脑
Of course you still have a best friend. And no, I am not brainwashed.
而我和Dyson和Lauren的关系 从来都不是完美的
And as far as Dyson and Lauren go, it's not like it was ever perfect.
Dyson放弃了他的爱
Dyson gave his love away
从此就变成了天字第一号王八蛋
and then he became an a-hole for like forever.
我们叫他无聊的贱人
We called him Mopey Dick.
接着我和Lauren交往 伤透了他的心
And then I broke his heart with Lauren,
现在她和M女王你浓我浓
and now she's all buddy buddy with the Morrigan.
糟透了
All bad things.
但是和Rainer不同
But with Rainer.
我终于觉得我能给这段关系做点贡献了
I finally feel like I have provided something
我打破了他的诅咒
to a relationship.I broke his curse.
我们渴望同样的东西 这样的感觉在爱之上
We want the same things. It's bigger than love.
我很抱歉我没跟你敞开心怀 Kenzi
And I am sorry if I locked you out, Kenzi.
我只是需要多一些时间
I just needed some time.
你使我的生命更完整
You complete me.
Hale让Kenzi搬去和他一起住
Hale asked Kenzi to move in with him.
什么?
What?
八字还没一撇呢
We don't know that yet. Okay.
他只是说想要谈谈 他说这很重要
He just needs to talk. Says it's important.
也很吓人
Also known as terrifying.
你要离开我了吗?
You're leaving me?
这种事儿发生在你头上时不好受吧?
Sucks when it happens to you, huh?
过来吧亲 我听到王八蛋那就原谅你了
Oh, come here you. You had me at a-hole.
听到王八蛋那就原谅你了
You had me at a-hole.
现在下楼 零食得配饮料
Now, go downstairs. Snacks needs drinks.
我都教你什么了?
Have I taught you nothing?
教太多了 我会回来的
So much. I'll be right back.
啊
Aagh!
一般来说这样你就挂了诶
This is usually the part where you die.
你一定是Bo了吧...
And you must be Bo...
本作品片源来自互联网，仅供个人影视制作学习交流之用
任何组织和个人不得公开传播或用于任何商业盈利用途
挪威金毛的胡须最有爱了字幕组  ╮(╯▽╰)╭
英文字幕：来自互联网
翻译：Neffititi 骷髅头正宫_K
精校：Neffititi Joy
发布：百度贴吧Tamsin后援群
资源下载请关注瓦尔基里字幕组官方微博
4x11 - End of a Line
你不是死了吗!
You're supposed to be dead!
该说啥好呢 姐就是那么幸运
What can I say? I'm just a lucky girl.
新的吗?
New?
Massimo给我从残肢上长出来的
Massimo grew it on to my stump.
你怎么被砍手的?
How'd you lose the hand?
流浪者派他的乌鸦们砍的
The Wanderer had his crows cut it off
因为我的门徒没有及时的把你
because my protégé here didn't deliver you
送到他面前
as quickly as he wanted.
Hugin和Munin背叛了Rainer 说不定是他俩自己决定要砍的
Hugin and Munin betrayed Rainer.They could have been acting alone.
所以你俩现在结婚了吗?
So you two are on a first name basis now?
他是她男朋友
He's her boyfriend.
姐扯了
And, I'm out.
Acacia等一下
Okay, Acacia, wait.
这可不是什么社交聚会 Tamsin
This wasn't a social call Tamsin.
我现在是亡灵猎人 只是凑巧有人
I'm a revenant hunter now, it's just a lucky coincidence that
想要杀死你的朋友
someone was trying to kill your friend here.
亡灵
Revenant?
死去的异种复活 为人操控使用
Dead Fae risen from the dead to settle old scores.
非常高效率 Acacia和我以前经常用他们
Very effective. Acacia and I used to use them all the time.
我们得和你那小白脸谈谈 马上
We need to talk to your boytoy. Now.
他昨晚离开了
He left late last night.
他去了战场 缅怀死去的人
He went to the battlefield. To pay respects to the dead.
或者复苏他们
Yeah or to re-animate them.
不 不可能
No. No way.
你对疯狂火车男到底有多了解
What do you really know about Crazy Train?
我知道我打破了他的诅咒
I know that I broke his curse.
我知道他是好人
And I know that he's a good guy.
怎么知道的?
How?
你觉得如果他想杀我 我会察觉不到吗?
You don't think I would know if he wanted to kill me?
我就是知道
I just know.
我看看 R开头的名字对吧 什么都没
Let's see. R, right? Nothing.
这本书记载了我们所有的历史
These books have every moment of our history in them
而他不在记录之中 为什么?
and he's no where to be found. Why?
Rainer从哪来的?
Where's Rainer?
好 拿上你的衣服
Alright. Get your coats.
我们去哪里?你俩是砖家
- Where are we going?
You two are the experts.
我们去看看到底谁在复活死人
Let's find out who's really raising the dead.
证明Rainer不是幕后操纵者
Prove that Rainer isn't behind this.
小伙伴们 真实难以置信
Guys, unbelieveable.
你们的男盆友要来的时候
Seriously, would I leave a dead body on the floor
老娘有在地板上留具尸体招待吗?
if her boyfriend was coming over?
欢迎光临
Thanks for coming.
恩恩
Yeah well
你不是应该外出恢复信仰吗?
Aren't you supposed to be out restoring the faith? Huh?
散布好消息
Spreading the good word?
叮咚 Una Mens挂了
Ding dong, the Una Mens are dead?
还在散布我悲痛的慰问呢
Still drafting my condolences.
这可不是我想像中的光明派临时领导的语气
That's not the tune I was expecting from the acting leader of the Light.
我以前是国王
I used to be a King.
恐怕也没有做得太好
Didn't do that very well either I'm afraid.
摆脱 这里乃至爱尔兰的小孩子都知道
Come on, every kid from here to Hibernia
你悠长光荣的英雄世纪
knows the tales of your long and glorious reign.
历史是赢家写出来的
History is written by the victors.
历史是用血写出来的
History is written in blood.
他驶于骏马之上
"And so he rode upon on his noble steed
割开血管 打败了反抗军
and cut down the vile insurgent, thus ending the rebellion
为大地带来了和平
and bringing peace to the land."
不管我做什么 Rainer总是知道答案
No matter what I did, Rainer always had an answer
总是早我十步
always ten steps ahead.
他的天赋就是预言 我除了用我的血 毫无选择
His gift is Foresight. I had no choice but to use my blood.
我写下他的军队背叛了他
I wrote that his armies betrayed him.
他以前很邪恶 是吗?
He was evil wasn't he?
只是目中无人 和我外孙女一样
Just defiant. Like my granddaughter.
这我必须同意
Yeah well I can't argue with that.
这个世界上有真正的邪恶存在 Vex
There's real evil in the world, Vex.
真正的恐惧 Garuda很邪恶
Real terrors. The Garuda was evil.
还有Pyrippus
The Pyrippus.
*Pyrippus 传说为冥王拉战车的长着蝙蝠翅膀的地狱之马*
那是真正的邪恶
That's real evil.
Pyrippus吗?
The Pyrippus?
拜托 蝙蝠翅膀的马?说真的
Come on.  Bat winged horse? Honestly.
你遇见哥斯拉的机会还能多点
You got a better chance of meeting Godzilla.
我可以做个更好的国王的
I should have been a better king.
对的 我们中谁没有点悔恨呢?
Yeah well... who amongst us doesn't have any regrets, eh?
是的 过节的时候 我如果没有为了保命背叛家人
Yeah, there be a fewer empty seats 'round the old holiday
桌子上还能多几双筷子呢
roast if I hadn't betrayed my own family to save my own hide.
你的父亲 Clust 是我见过的最勇敢的人之一
Your father, Clust, was one of the bravest men I've ever known.
拜托 他特马就是个打鱼的啊
Oh, come on. He was a bloody fisherman.
你怎么认识他?
Why the hell would you know him?
他是我最好的将军 他是个英雄
He was my best general. He was a hero.
不 我的父亲觉得小孩就该安静听话
No, my father believed that kids should be seen and not heard.
他从来不喜欢我的笑话 他从来没喜欢过我
He never liked my jokes. He never liked me at all.
我对我的父亲一无所知 我也无所谓
I never knew my father. And that suited him just fine.
你想要知道什么?
What do you want to know?
希望不是个死粽子
Hey, hopefully not-a-dead-dude
而是我的腹肌性感猛男
but my abs-olicious sex machine.
噢卖糕的 Dimitri
Oh my god, Dimitri.
嘿
Hey.
嗨 你 你来这干嘛?
Hi, wh... what are you doing here?
我们来看你呀
We come to see you!
啊 69年的科迈罗 黄色 你的吗?
Uh, 69 Camaro. Yellow. Yours?
不是 我室友的
Uh no, my roommate's.
风紧 扯呼
Uh, call it off.
你说什么?我们?
What do you mean... we?
小阳光呀
Solnushka.
* Solnushka 俄语中意为  太阳*
妈
Mom.
这是什么地方?
What is this place?
人们不想被找到的时候就来这里
Where people go when they  don't want to be found.
或者当他们出城的时候
Or to find someone to  carry out their dirty work.
来这里找人帮他们做点粗活
If they're out of town.
Raine没有做这些
Rainer didn't do this.
啊哈?
Uh huh?
那告诉我 Rainer王国的天气怎么样?
Tell me, what's the weather like in Rainer-land?
阴森暴雨?阳光阴影?
Dark and stormy? Sunny and shady?
我警告你...
I am warning you...
你俩能消停点吗?
Would you two focus?
这里是死人聚集地
This is where the Cults of the Dead hang out.
如果Rainer雇佣了亡灵 或者他没有
If Rainer hired revenants, or if he didn't,
他会来找这些人 我们马上就知道了
these would be the guys he'd go through. We'll know soon enough.
瞧瞧 你的男朋友送了一个尖叫电报过来
Awww look. Your boyfriend sent a grunting telegram.
不是他
It's not him.
打头
Heads it is.
抱歉来晚了 堵车揪心啊
Sorry, I'm late. Traffic was a bitch.
你想要个新冰箱吗?
Hey. You need new fridge?
或许吧
Uh, maybe.
我会给你这台自动售货机卖个好价钱的
I get you good price for this vending machine.
别卖我的东西了
Stop selling my stuff.
你表哥只想帮忙而已
Your cousin just try to help.
上次他想帮忙 我的身份就被盗窃了
Well last time he tried to help,  someone stole my identity.
记得吗?
Remember?
那绝对是个误会啊!
A total misunderstanding!
顺便说一下如果警察打来询问假支票的事情
By the way if police call about a string of bad checks
你最好跑路
best just to leave town.
你现在又做了什么?!
What have you done now?!
绝壁是个误会啊
Total misunderstanding, yeah?
拜托 我们能不能别吼了
Please, can we stop this yelling.
如果我没记错 我们一家人没事就是对吼
If I remember correctly, all we do in this family is yell.
你去哪了 妈妈?
Where have you been, Mom?
你好 你好
Hello, hello.
听说如果我想找俄罗斯公主的话 必须到这个地方来
Heard if I'm lookin' for a fine Russian princess this is the place.
嗨 时机不对 瓦斯泄露了
Hey, um, really bad time. Gas leak.
瓦斯泄漏...
Gas leak...
杀人鼠魔
Killer rats.
到底发生什么了?
What's goin' on?
我家人来了 他们就这么不请自来了
My family's here. They just showed up.
我和他们可不一样 她只不过生了我而已
Okay, I'm nothing like them. She's only my mother by birth.
Kenzi没关系
Kenzi, it's okay.
我邀请他们来的
I invited them.
你居然对我做这种事
You did this to me?
你以为Harvey看见我们会很高兴?
You think Harvey is gonna be happy to see us?
我像抓狗一样捉住了他妈
Well, I hunted down his Mom like a dog
然后把她送去了荷可巴监狱 所以...
then delivered her to Hecuba prison, so...
好你在外面等着
Okay, you can wait outside.
谢谢你来
Thank you for coming.
我搭档叫我 所以我来了
Well my partner called so I came.
Dyson
Dyson...
D大叔和我去和居民谈谈
Hey, the D Man and I are gonna go talk to the locals.
看他们知道什么 你和Acacia进去吧
See what they know. You can go in with Acacia.
好的
Okay.
谢谢你 搭档
Thanks, partner.
恩
Yeah.
所以你就是那个让我家Tamsin相信她可以变得更好的人
So you're the one who convinced my Tamsin she could be more.
有问题吗?
Something wrong with that?
当然没问题
Absolutely nothing.
Tamsin很爱你
Tamsin really loves you
我从她的蓝眼睛里看得出
I can see it in her baby blues.
恩 但是...?
Mm-hmm. But...?
你要和她作对的话
You get on the wrong side of her again
我不会给你苟延残喘的机会
I won't leave you with enough Chi to turn and cough.
我只不过跟随了流浪者 因为我别无选择
All I did was side with The Wanderer because I had no choice.
听着耳熟?
Sound familiar?
啧啧啧
Well, well, well.
这不是我最爱的胆大包天 装饰过人的Valkyrie吗?
If it isn't my favorite ball busting, overly-accessorized Valkyrie.
你什么时候把嘴贱金毛换成了
So when'd you trade in bitchy and blonde for a...
胸部大如圣诞节火腿的棕毛?
brunettte with bouncy Christmas hams?
Harvey 你不会还在因为Tamsin捆了你妈妈而生气吧?
Harvey...you're not still mad at Tamsin 'cause hogtied your mother?
因为贵母上真的很胖 她也没办法啊
'Cause your mom was really fat, she kinda had no choice.
喂 覆水难收
Hey. Water under the bridge.
不过如果你看见那个北欧疯子 你告诉她
But if you do see that Nordic nut tease, you tell her
让我吐两口唾沫 给她几记胳膊肘 就能弥补
she can make it up to me with a little spit and elbow grease.
哈
Hah.
啊!
Aghhh!
哦耶 哦耶宝贝
Oooh yeah. Oh yeah baby.
做好点
Make it good.
谁控制着那个僵尸 Harvey?
Who owns the head, Harvey?
哈 你确定不是你们其中一个人吗 你两跟双胞胎一样
Huh? Are you sure it ain't one of yours? You two could be twins.
嘿 放着我来
Hey, hey.  I got this.
你好 我是Bo
Hi. I'm Bo.
淫妖吗?
The Succubus?
告诉我们想要的消息 Harvey?
Now why don't you tell us what we want to know, Harvey?
我会为你做任何事
I'd do anything for you.
我还想对你为所欲为
And I'd do everything to you.
干完
Bottoms up.
恩
Mmm... mmm.
有一点果酒香
There's a fruity bouquet.
夹杂着樱桃和肥料的味道 他一定吓坏了
Hints of cherry and manure.He must have been scared.
但是有点难说到底是恐惧 还是土地
But it's hard to tell the terror from the terroir.
你读书的时候 在学校朝天吐口水
You were that kid in school who spit in the air
然后又自己伸手接住 是吧?
then catch it again, weren't you?
喝血是获得亡灵控制权的唯一方式
Drinking blood is the only way to gain dominion
或者找到谁拥有控制权
over a revenant... or find out who currently has it.
神啊 快点 我快吐了...
Oh god. Quickly, before I vomit...
你知不知道幕后者是谁?
do you know who's behind this?
恩 不是我的人
Yeah, it ain't one of mine.
谁操控着这死人?
Who owns this dead?
恩 这真是意外中的意外啊 淫妖
Well, ain't that the kicker, Succubus.
这死人...
This dead...
是她的
belongs to her.
这死人是你搞的
This is your dead!
别抓老娘的皮外套
Hands off the leather.
那是我的台词
That's my line.
哦女人打架
Ooh, cat-fight.
对 我好想真杀了他
Oh. Yeah, I might have killed the guy.
我没复活他
But I didn't raise him from the dead.
抓她的头发
Pull her hair!
你就是个雇佣杀手 这些邪恶东西就是你搞的
You're nothing but a hired killer! This evil shit is right up your alley.
别装得像你真知道什么一样
Don't you even pretend to know a thing about me!
我要真想让谁三更死 丫就别想活过五更
If I was here to kill anybody, they would be dead already.
姐就是那么牛x
I am that good.
无聊 撕她的衣服
Boring. Rip her shirt open.
你怎么样?
How you holding up?
没有再好了
Never better.
你敢骗老娘?
Are you lying to me?
真的没有再好了
Never better.
要说安慰的话 我觉得她是彻底疯了!
Well if it's any consolation I think she's crazy.
我没疯
I am not crazy!
你要帮忙吗?
Can we help you with something?
帮帮我!帮帮我?
Help me! Help me?
哦 没什么能帮得了我
Oh, there can be no help for me.
但也许 也许能有什么能帮你们
But there may be...there may be help for you.
很久以前有三姐妹 都有魔法
Long ago there were three sisters and they were all magic
只有一个活下来了 因为她能控制死人
but only one survived because she could control the dead.
她把她从我这带走了
She took her from me.
她带走她 就像流水线上拿走一件衣服似的
She took her like a shirt from a clothesline.
既死又活 既死又活
Dead and alive. Dead and alive.
她既死又活
She was dead and alive.
等等你说什么?
Hey. Wait. What did you say?
她能控制死人
She can control the dead.
她既死又活  她把她从我这带走了
She is dead and alive. She took her from me.
她把她从我这带走了!
She took her from me!!
她既死又活 曾经有三 今仅余一
She's dead and alive. There were three and there's one.
她既死又活 既死又活
And she is dead and alive. She is dead and alive.
打她胸口!
Ah. Punch her in the tit!
你们干嘛呢?
What is going on?
没什么
Nothing.
怎么了?
What's up?
Dyson和我找到线索了 叫什么Leveau的女人
Dyson and I actually found a lead. Some woman named Laveau.
恩
Hmph.
账单拿来 姐赔
Send me a bill.
Mackenzie
Mackenzie?
*Kenzi的全名*
你为什么这么生气 亲?
Why are you so mad, baby?
你真的要问吗?
Are you seriously going to ask me that?
看看我给你带了你小时候
Look. I brought my earrings that you love so much
最喜欢的耳环 很漂亮吧?
when you were a little girl. Aren't they beautiful?
你的男朋友毁了我的人生 妈
Your boyfriend ruined my life, Mom.
Bodgen 是个很复杂的人...
Bodgen, is complicated man...
我知道他叫什么
I know his name.
我知道我错了
Look, I know I make mistake.
我觉得你还是小孩时我喝酒喝太多...
I know I drink too much when you were a little baby...
我应该保护你的
I... I should have protect you.
我也只是没长大的孩子!
I was just a little girl too!
妈 你真的假的...
Please, Mom...
我根本没有想到我可以独立生活
I never believe that I have the strength to stand on my own.
我以为我需要他
I always think I need the man.
我是个小孩 妈 我流落街头
I was a little girl, Mom. And I was living on the street
因为你在我和那个混蛋间选择了后者
because you chose that bastard over me.
你知道我花了多久...才回到正常人生活吗?
Do you know how long it took me to... to feel normal again?
我知道...
I know...
不 你不知道
No. You don't know.
在遇到Bo之前 我就是偷摸扒窃...
And before I met Bo I lived off what I could steal and I...
我身处窘境 自己都觉得羞耻
I was in some situations that not only am I ashamed off
我都不信我还活下来了
but I just can't believe that I even survived.
我让他滚蛋了
I kick him out.
什么?
What?
对 他消失了 真的 白白了
Oh yes. He's gone. Yup. So long.
那是什么时候的事?
When did that happen?
六个月前
Six months ago.
可...我不知道你在哪...
But I... I didn't know how to find you...
你那好男人Hale打给我了 我必须来
But then when your nice man Hale call, I think, I have to come.
我必须得来见见我的小阳光
I have to come and see my little Solnushka.
你有你生父的力量
You have the strength of your father.
愿他灵魂安息
God rest his soul.
我很担心你 我觉得总有一天他会
I've been really worried about you.I thought one day he would...
你做了正确的事
You did the right thing. You did.
好了 没事了
Okay. It's settled.
今晚我们来庆祝
Tonight we celebrate.
哦 穿点漂亮的 你怎么一身黑
Oh, and uh, put on something nice! So much black.
你会很漂亮的
You could be a very pretty girl.
好吧 帮帮忙妹子 解释下...
Okay. So, help me out here...
流浪者一下火车
The Wanderer gets off the train
就开始玩过家家了?
and suddenly starts playing house?
怎么了?
What is it?
恩自从他回来了 下了火车后...
Um, since he's came back, since he got off the train...
我开始记得一些事情
I've been remembering things.
很模糊...
They're really fuzzy...
什么记忆?
What things?
好吧 大反叛后 我把Rainer的灵魂
Well, I may have given the Rainer's
给了血王
soul to the Blood King after the great rebellion.
我没带他去英灵殿
I didn't take it to Valhalla.
你把他弄上火车的?
You put him on that train?
我出了点力...把他变成了流浪者
I helped...make him the Wanderer.
我们得干掉他
We gotta take him out.
Acacia...
你和我都知道那男人就是个噩耗
Oh, you know as well as I do that that man is bad news.
就因为他和那边那位美女搞不清
Just because he's bonin' Sugar Snatch
你以为他会放你好好生活吗
up there doesn't mean that he's gonna leave you be.
在你干过那些事后?
After what you've done?
天啊Tamsin Rainer的亡灵是冲你去的
Jesus, Tamsin, Rainer's revenants are after you.
迷人的地方 谁又是Laveau?
Charming place. Who is this Laveau anyway?
她是个巫毒女祭司 孩子
She's a voodoo priestess, child.
我愿意效劳 淫妖
And my gifts are at your service, Succubus.
你知道我?
You know me?
人人都知道你 妹子
Everybody knows you, girl.
你铲除了讨厌的议会
You took out the high council of hate.
还和神秘男纸恋爱
And are involved with a man of mystery.
你知道什么?
What do you know of it?
我知道你感受过的那种疯狂的爱 狼叔
I know you've felt that crazy kind of love, Wolf.
我看过你的野兽之心了
I've seen into your animal heart.
可你什么时候才能明白这是你自己制造的牢笼
But when you gonna see its prison is wholly of your own makin'?
好了 很有趣 啊哈哈 但是
Okay, this is fun and everything but, uh
我们口袋里装了个人头
we got a head in a bag.
我要知道是谁派他来杀我的
I'd like to find out who sent it to kill me.
你要让我复生亡灵?
You want me to wake up the dead?
我复生各种亡灵!
I wake up all the dead!
Massimo说这是他重新制造的
Massimo told me that he built this from scratch
啊 肮脏的骗子 不要脸的掘墓者...
ugh dirty lying, son of a,grave robbing...
小心!
Watch out!
你 这是你指使的
You! You're behind this!
你有我要的东西 淫妖!
You have what I seek, Succubus!
你要的?你要的啥?
Seek? Seek what?
恶魔的坐骑
The Devil's horse.
Pyrippus要来了 我得保护我自己
The Pyrippus is coming! And I need to protect myself.
当那五个人死了以后
When the prize of the five, was all made dead
他们的力量便合为一体 我要那个
their powers was sewn into one... and I wants it!
你在说毛呢?
What are you talking about?
种子!
The seed!
我来抬脚好了
I'll get her feet.
哇
Wow.
哇 Galina  我得告诉你
Oh wow.Galina, I have to tell you.
这是我这辈子吃过的最好吃的饭了
That was one of the best meals I've had in my entire life.
当然了 我的小Kenzi有帮忙嘛
Of course it was. My little Mackenzie helped.
基本原则老妈 别吹过头了
Baby steps mom. Don't over do it.
胡说
Oh nonsense.
你一直都很会做俄罗斯酸奶薄饼
You were always so good  at making Oladyi dish.
这妹子将来一定能当个好老婆
This one is going to make you a very good wife.
天啊 妈...
Oh my god, Mom...
恩
Oi...
对不起 太尴尬了
I'm sorry, that's embarrassing.
好吧 应该是好时候了吧大概
Okay. Well, good time as any I guess.
好了 好了
Okay. Okay.
恩...
Uh...
干嘛?
What?
要是没有你妈妈的祝福
I wouldn't feel right doing this
我觉得这样做不太合适
without asking for your Mother's blessing.
我滴神啊
Oh my god.
就感受我的心吧 Kenzi
Just feel my heart, Kenzi.
只要在你身边 它就跳得疯狂
Whenever I'm around you it loses control.
从我们相识那一刻起 我从你那不可思议的
From the moment we met and I saw who you are
蓝眼睛里看到了你
behind those ridiculously beautiful blue eyes,
我知道你就是那个人
I knew you were the one.
没人让我这么欢乐开怀
Nobody makes me laugh like you do.
没人让我想要变得更好
Nobody makes me want to be a better man.
没人像你这么和我对着干
No one does the exact opposite of everything that I say like you do.
小妈咪
Lil mama.
哦天啊
Oh my god.
你愿意嫁给我吗
Will you marry me?
你好
Hello?
Dimka 你来真的吗?
Dimka? Seriously?
对不起 是Bodgen 他想要知道
Sorry, it's Bodgen, he wants to know
你今晚还是明天去汇款?
can he expect money tomorrow or will you wire tonight?
Durak!
我现在没空哈...
Kinda in the middle of somethin' here...
啥?
What?
哦 恩 你爸 他想借点钱
Oh, well your father he, uh, wanted to borrow
启动资金
- some start up money.
他不是我爸!
That man is not my father!
你骗了我?
You lied to me?
亲爱的 这不是什么大事...
Babe, it's not a big deal...
Hale 这是大事 对吧?
Hale, it is a big deal, okay?
你要知道点好...就别管这事
If you know what's good for you... you'll stay out of this.
出去
Get out.
别啊 小阳光 亲爱的 别这样...
No, Solnushka. Baby, please...
不!出去!现在
No! Get out! Now.
我们知道谁在控制亡灵了
We found out who's controlling the revenants.
是Laveau
It was Laveau.
她还让Acacia体验了下鬼玩人
She's also got Acacia doing a little Evil Dead routine.
*The Evil Dead  中译鬼玩人 1981年的恶灵苏醒类恐怖片*
我们需要你的帮助
We need your help.
你的手下没拿到我们想要的东西 对吧?
I guess your boys didn't get us what we need, huh, baby?
恩
Mm-hmm.
我们?
We?
那应该是个"不"  Dyson...?
That'd be a "no." Dyson... ?
啊 尽管你死了...
Ah. Even though you're dead...
你还是我见过的最漂亮的贱人
you are still the hottest bitch I've ever seen.
死人?
Dead?
人皆有一死 淫妖!
There's no escape Succubus!
把种子给我们 不然就去死吧!
Give us the Una Mens seed or die!
活死人!
Dead!
那些你拖车外面的尸体
Those other bodies sitting outside your trailer.
是你的换洗衣服吗?
Change of clothes?
你是亡灵头领对吧?
You're the "head" revenant, aren't you?
控制亡灵的唯一方法就是
The only way to gain dominion over a revenant is...
噢
Oh.
恶心!
Eugh!
都归你了
She's all yours.
都散了啊
Be at peace.
哦 求求你一定带了薄荷糖
Oh. Please tell me you have a mint.
Kenzi 你听我解释...
Kenzi, please let me explain...
不要 他对我做了那么多坏事 你视而不见
No! All the horrible shit he did to me and you did nothing.
要不是你不听话 他是不会那样的!
He wouldn't of done those things if you weren't so defiant!
你知道吗 我一直以为你也是受害者
You know I always thought you were a victim.
我还以为你是害怕 可并不是
I always thought you were scared. But you're not scared.
你就是个懦夫 连你自己都看不起
You're just a coward who doesn't value herself
又怎能尊重自己的孩子
so how can she value her own children.
再见了
Goodbye.
听着 恩 你和这汉子 他 恩 挺好
Listen, uh, you and this guy. He's uh good.
别拒绝他成吗
Don't call it off.
那么 你想谈谈吗?
So, you want to talk about it?
不太想
Not really.
就老实说吧
Be honest with me.
要我诚实吗?
You want me to be honest, huh?
是的
Yes.
你和Lauren在一起 至少我知道她心地善良
At least with Lauren I knew she cared.
这个流浪者 这个...
This Wanderer, this...
Rainer
Rainer.
我对他一无所知 你也是
I don't know anything about him. And neither do you.
Dyson...
你怎么能知道他不是
How do you know he's not
来向Trick复仇的?
here just to get back at Trick for cursing him?
你尽可以觉得你自己受伤了...
You have every right to be hurt...
Bo 我会一直在你身边
Bo, I will always be there for you.
我会帮你刷怪打坏人
I'll will stand by you and help you fight the bad guy.
但要是这人 Rainer 变成了坏人...
But if this guy... if this Rainer turns out to be the bad guy...
我不认为我可以帮你什么
I don't think I can help you with that.
你不是那意思
You can't mean that.
你和我 我们一直不仅仅是恋人
You and I, we were always more than just lovers.
我知道
I know.
那我们现在是什么?
And what are we now?
听着 这个命运哥的事确实很难理解
Look, this whole destiny  thing is hard to understand
相信我 我也不是一时就接受的...
believe me, I am having trouble with it too...
这人绑架了你
The man kidnapped you.
不 他没有
No, he didn't.
不是那样的...
It wasn't like that...
那是怎样的?
Then what was it like?
说来话长
It is a long story.
听着 换了我也会支持你 当我还...
Look, I would have stood by you too, when I was...
当你还怎样?
When you were what?
当你还爱着我的时候?
Still in love with me?
你不是总能选你要走的路的 Dyson
You can't always choose your path, Dyson.
你似乎一直都可以
You seem to.
不可能!
No way!
他真的站马背上扔了剑
He actually stood on his horse and threw the sword.
刀还在半空中时 他用了他的能力
And as the sword flew through the air he used his mesmer
让那士兵张开双臂
to make the soldier thrust his arms out wide
迎接刺向他心脏的剑!
and welcome the sword into his heart!
不可能
No way.
那真是传奇
It was legendary.
那是什么?
What is that?
吾之书...
My books...
Rainer真的被写回历史了
Rainer is being written back into history. Literally.
听着 多谢你
Listen. Thank you.
我超喜欢玩毛团
And as much as I love a good yarn.
你知道的就跟疯兔子一样
You know, like the March Hare.
*March Hare 爱丽丝镜中奇遇的角色 是只疯狂的兔子*
我要迟到了 得去参加个重要的订婚仪式
I'm late, I'm late for a very important engagement.
Vex 种子呢?
Vex. The seed?
第六个una mens的种子 失踪了
The sixth Una Mens seed. It's missing.
有人从我这拿走了
Someone's taken it from me.
果然你认为和我有关
And of course you think I have something to do with that.
你拿了吗?
Did you?
亡羊补牢 Vex 我知道你有好的一面
It's not too late, Vex.I see the good in you.
我在你身上看得见你父亲
I see your father in you.
拿那种子的人根本不知道那会释放多可怕的力量
Whoever has that seed has no idea what kind of power it can unleash.
你能阻止难以想像的痛苦
You can stop more suffering than anyone's has ever known.
你觉得我有好的一面?
You see good in me, yeah?
那只是你的想法罢了
Well at least that makes one of us.
Vex 别干傻事 Vex!
Vex, don't be a fool. Vex!
Vex!
很高兴和你再次合作 小美女
It was really nice working with you again, baby girl.
是啊 真是大开眼界
Yup. It was a real eye opener.
你啥意思?
What do you mean?
我爱你Acacia 我们一起经历了好多事
I love you Acacia and we've been through a lot together.
但我们都知道没人
But we both know that no one
雇佣你追踪那个亡灵 对吧?
hired you to track that revenants, did they?
什么?当然有了
What? Of course they did.
你要布置那张塔罗牌
You needed somewhere to put the Tarot card.
然后我们就会去搞死流浪者
So I'd get my team on side and we'd take The Wanderer out.
你在说什么呢?
What are you talking about?
别骗我 Acacia
Do not lie to me, Acacia.
你知道他的能力
You know the things he's capable of.
你知道他都干了什么
You know the things he's done.
我不再杀人了
I'm just not a killer anymore.
他砍了我的手!
He took my hand!
他要真是那样的人 我会第一个干掉他
If he's what I think he is I'll be the first person to slit Rainer's throat.
但这次我不能再犯错了 我得先确定
But I'm gonna do it right this time. I have to be sure.
你要怎么办 Tamsin?
What are you gonna do, Tamsin?
你要找只狼 安定下来
Gonna go find yourself a little wolf. Settle down.
再生几个狼崽子...
Squeeze out a couple of puppies...
再见了 卡莎
Bye, 'Cac.
恩 好吧 那就这样
Mm-hmm. Okay, then.
噢 对了 你可别放松警惕
Oh, listen. You might want to keep your wits about you.
Massimo要有大动作
Massimo is up to something big.
Massimo死了
Massimo's dead.
咱俩都知道死了不代表死透了
And you and I both know that "dead" don't always mean dead.
哦 嘿 听着
Oh, hey. Look.
这个雨人哥的事 我知道
This whole Rainer thing I know it makes me look
我就跟疯了一样 我也有疑问
kind of insane, but I have questions for him.
真的 但是我无法忽视自己的感觉
I do. But I can't ignore how I feel.
有时候你就得跟着感觉走 对吧?
Sometimes you just have to go for it. Right?
对啊...
Right...
这特么怎么回事...
What the hell...
这宇宙大帅哥是谁?
Hello. Who is the historical hottie?
你啥意思?这是Rainer 是你老板啊
What do you mean? It's Rainer. That's your boss.
这不是我老板
That's not my boss.
我必须承认 高富帅
Gotta hand it to you rich boy.
你可真会选戒指
You sure do know how to pick out the bling.
对不起 Kenzi
I'm sorry, Kenzi.
哇!!
Whoa!!
别裸奔啊 大哥!
Put those away, sir!
我就试试嘛
It was worth a shot.
我觉得...
I think that...
我们还是慢点的好
we just need to slow down a bit.
我们还有时间啊 Hale
Because we have so much time, Hale.
我们有的是时间
We have all the time in the world.
我只是 不想重复我妈的老路
And I just...don't want to be my mother.
我不想冒失的做决定然后被困其中...失去自我
I don't want to rush into things and feel trapped. And lose...me.
我答应了我自己永远不会那样
I promised myself that I would never do that.
你不是真的要拒绝我吧?
You're not lettin' me down easy, are you?
你疯了吗?
Are you crazy?
你真觉得我会拒绝
Did you really think that I would let the best
一个我遇到过的最好最完美的男人
most amazing, wonderful man I have ever met
让他从我指间溜走?
slip through my stupid, stubborn fingers?
恩?
Hmm?
啊!!
Ah!!
我滴神啊 你在这太好
Oh my god.Thank god you are here.
今天真是...
I mean today has just been...
我都不知道发生了些什么...
I don't even know what's going on but...
我知道...
I'm what's going on...
当当当当!
Shazam!
天啊 你和Hale?
Oh my god! You and Hale?
对 对 我是说 "是的"!
Yeah. Yeah! I mean "yes!"
但我...还没有说我愿意
But I... but I haven't said yes yet. But...
还没有!
You said "yet!"
我知道
I know.
我知道 很疯狂对吧?哇...
I know.This is crazy, right? Whoa...
光是想想我在考虑就已经很疯了
That's crazy that I'm even like considering this.
不你不疯 一点也不
No. No you are not crazy. At all.
他在楼上?
Is he upstairs?
是
Yeah.
不不不 没穿裤子呢!
Oh no no! No pants! No pants!
哦...哦!
Oh... Oh!
好吧 我去弄点零食!
Okay. Well I'll go and get some snacks!
还有酒!
And Wine!
还有糖果
And candy.
很多糖果
Lots of candy.
好
Okay.
你在这干嘛呢 傻x?
How are you doing there, champ?
好几百年没觉得这么孤单了 挺好
Haven't felt this alone in centuries. Feels good.
你还记得那天我们在拳击室见面?
Do you remember that day we first met... at the boxing ring?
我记得你照我嘴上来了几拳
I remember taking some shots in the mouth, yeah.
我照你嘴上来的可不只是拳头吧
That's not all I did to that mouth.
Tamsin 我现在脑子一团乱...
Tamsin, I can't even think straight right now...
别想了
Stop thinking.
你想太多
You're always thinking.
来啊
Come on.
亲 你要奶酪还是冰激凌...
Hey baby? Do you want cheese or ice cream...
要不我们用奶酪直接配冰激凌?
or should we put the cheese directly into the ice cream?
这主意不错
I like that idea.
或者还不如你去死
Or you could just die already.
Hale!Hale!!
Hale! Hale!!!
啊 啊 我从来没觉得你声音好听过
Ah, ah, ah, ah. I never did like the sound of your voice.
啊!
Agh!
Ahhh!
你和那傻逼淫妖贱人
You and that stupid bitch Succubus
就不知道少管闲事对吧 你要杀我?!
just couldn't leave it alone, could you? You tried to kill me?
活活烧死我?!
Burn me alive?!
啊啊啊啊啊啊
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ahh.
现在我要把你变得和我一样满脸开花
Now, I'm gonna make you pretty just like me.
Hale!
怎么了 小猫咪?
What's the matter, kitten?
你怎么不用你的闪闪火花把我闪走?
Why don't you just use your little sparkle and sparkle me away?
哦对了你不行了
Oh that's right you can't.
因为你不过是个可悲的人类
Because you are just a pathetic little human
跟我一样
just like me.
但愿你活得愉快 德鲁伊
I hope you had a good life, druid.
不!别!
No! Please!
啊!!
Gah!!
我滴神啊!
Oh my god!
啊
Ugh!
什么...
What...
不 亲爱的!
No. Baby!
亲爱的...
Baby...
给扎莫拉族 赐予圣物
"To Clan Zamora, a gift bestowed
免疫邪恶
immune to evil deed, to blow.
携带此圣枝之人 永恒...
"For he who carries sacred twig. Immortality..."
妈呀这韵律太挫了我背不下去了
God the pentameter's so awful I can't even finish.
但这小东西可是救过我两次
But this little baby has saved my life twice now.
多谢你了哥们
Thanks for that big guy.
别碰他!
Don't you touch him!
说得对
You are right.
我应该感谢你
I should be thanking you.
你欠我的债算清了
Consider us paid in full.
吸气 你没事的
Breathe. You're okay.
我爱你
I love you.
不 别啊
No, no.
不 不要这样 谁来帮帮我
No no! Someone help me please.
求你了 谁来帮忙啊!
Please, anybody!
Bo你在哪里?
Bo where are you?
你在哪?不...
Where are you...No!
Kenzi 你俩搞完了吗 我要一醉方休
Kenzi! I hope you are done 'cause I want to get d-runk!
哦天啊 天啊
Oh my god...Oh my god!
发生了什么事?
What happened?
Massimo
Massimo.
都是Massimo干的 他杀了他 都是我的错
Massimo did this. He killed him. And it's all my fault.
Kenzi 什么?不
Kenzi, what? No.
天哪 Hale!
Oh god, Hale!
是圣枝
The twig.
你说什么呢?
What, what are you talking about?
我把那给了Massimo 为了得到能力
I gave it to Massimo for my power.
我那傻逼无极限的能力 都是我的错
My stupid stupid power! I did this.
Bo Bo 你能复活他的 你那个气的东西
Bo. Bo, you can bring him back. The Chi thing.
你可以复活他
You can bring him back.
你必须让他活过来
You have to bring him back.
不Kenzi 我不行...
No Kenzi, I can't...
Bo Dyson在你Dawning死的时候
Bo, when Dyson died after the Dawning
你吸了我们的气救了他 现在救救Hale啊
you sucked all of our chi and you brought him back, now bring back Hale.
Kenzi...
你必须这样做
You have to do it!
不Kenzi 没有足够的气啊
No Kenzi. There isn't enough Chi!
上次有Lauren Trick和Stella...
Last time there was, Lauren, and Trick, and Stella...
还有我 还有我呢 用我的气吧
And me. And me. Take it from me.
不我不能失去你!
No. I can't lose you!
你真特么的自私!
You are so goddamned selfish!
你总说你想帮助别人 可你只是为自己着想罢了!
You say you always want to help people but you only ever help yourself!
我不会原谅你的
I will never forgive you.
快点啊!
Do it!
Kenzi 我不能 我救不了他
Kenzi, I can't. I can't save him.
为什么?
Why?
你会死的
Because you'll die.
我不在乎
I don't care.
我在乎 我在乎
I do! I care.
我选你 我会永远选择你
I choose you. I will always choose you.
不我本来要说"我愿意"的 我本来要答应的!
No! I was gonna say "yes." I was gonna say "yes!"
我想答应的
I wanted to say "yes."
我知道
I know.
对不起 Kenzi 对不起
I'm so sorry, Kenzi. I'm so sorry.